Hi, I'm Macy and I'm here with Amy from
the research team and we're going to be
talking about Tessle verifiers today.
So Amy, maybe before we get into what
exactly they are and how they work,
maybe you could talk to me a bit about
the problem we're trying to solve.
>> Yeah. So what we've seen is that as
agents write more code and people write
code faster, there's been a real problem
at the review end. So PRs kind of pile
up and engineers end up having to review
lots and lots of PRs. They're trying to
kind of steer the agents to know follow
conventions that they care about or kind
of consistently make a good user
experience. It gets pretty overwhelming
to stay on top of all the PR. So we
started from that point of kind of
realizing well how can we give more
tools for expressing what you want from
the [music] code, what expectations
you've got, what invariants you want to
fix. So
there are a number of ways I feel to
kind of improve the reviewer [music]
experience and and one of them is code
review. How are verifiers meaningfully
different from code review?
>> So it sits basically between code review
and linting which would be how you do
kind of deterministic checks. So
somewhere in between where we still have
something that needs a little bit of
judgment, but we can make it into a
really clear rule that a single judge
call could look at a file and say yes,
that rule is followed. So it feels more
like a checklist than it feels like an
open-ended ask to an agent to go and
[music] investigate. So we've seen it
sit alongside code review really nicely
because what you can find is that in a
code review, the agents might be finding
the same kinds of things over and over
again or your human reviewers might find
the same things. So they might keep on
having to say to an agent,
>> you know, remember this detail that I
told you before. Remember this detail
before. And we don't want to then rely
on the agent always remembering to find
that thing. We want to codify that rule.
We want to make sure it gets followed
consistently.
>> Maybe we can dig into like [music] what
exactly a verifier is kind of what the
form factor is. So these are rules about
invariance that you want [music] to have
followed in your codebase that we can
check using a model as a judge. If I
give a couple examples from our own
codebase, we've got one that says in our
front end [music] whenever we show an
error message, we should also show you
what to do next about it. [music] Or we
say that all of our userfacing text
should be in US English, not UK [music]
English, which we have a hard time with
because we're in London and we'd like to
stick the use in in different words. So
this is another big difference with
[music]
uh having multiple rounds of code review
for example because these are narrow
rules you can afford to run them on
every single commit in a CI [music] and
that's what we do. So we run tens of
thousands of judgments and the bill is
normally around what one or two code
reviews u will cost.
>> Oh wow that's really cheap.
>> It's really cheap. Yeah.
>> So how do I get started with verifiers?
So, the simplest way to get started is
if you've installed our CLI [music] is
to talk to the Tessle agent in the CLI.
You can either go into that and just ask
it open-ended. How would I set up
verifiers? [music]
Or it's got a couple of nice loops that
you might want to run off the bat. You
can trigger. So, one of them is review
my PRs and tell me what I could do about
them. So, if you run that, [music] you
might find it suggests skill
improvements or llinters, but it might
also suggest [music] verifiers. Thank
you so much for showing me all things
verifiers. Um, really cool. Sounds
really powerful. If you guys want to get
started with Tesla verifiers, you can go
to tesla.io/agent
and you can ask the Tesla agent all
about them. Or you can visit our docs
and get started that way. Thanks for
watching. See you next time.